danraine.com 2013-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Dan Raine

Raine Ventures LLC. is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We provide certain services and opportunities for users of our web site and members of our organization. In order to provide these services, we require that you submit some personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.

## Information Gathered

When you register at this website or subscribe to one of our email lists we are collecting information from you. This information is necessary to communicate with you, to fulfil your requests regarding information and products, to provide you with any products you have purchased, and to contact you about your membership or other Raine Ventures LLC. products. Some of our web sites may also offer forums, please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge.

## Information Sharing

We will not sell, rent, or share your personally identifiable information with others, unless we have your permission or are required to do so by law.

## Emailing You

If you have subscribed to one of our email lists we will send you messages every now and then, these may be purely informational messages, they may be promotional messages for our own products or services, or they may contain recommendations for other people’s products or services. Our emails are never sent without permission and you will only receive these if you have subscribed to one of our email lists. All of our emails have an unsubscribe link in them so you can easily remove yourself from these mailings if you no longer wish to receive them.

## Use of Contractors

We may retain the service of outside contractors to perform services on our behalf (for example, to help provide technical support services or deliver new products or services). At times, we must disclose relevant personally identifiable information about you to our contractors so they may provide these specific services for us. We require our contractors to keep this information confidential and to only use the information on our behalf.

## Cookies

We use cookies on our site to manage your log in to our network of sites and for other site management purposes. Cookies are also used to manage our advertising system but you are not personally identifiable by these.

## Links to Third Party Web Sites

Our service may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites or software. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy and information collection practices.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may amend this policy occasionally. It is your responsibility to check this page for any notices of change.
